Viewers, I know you are ready and the Spirit of God is much around to set us free.
He has descended already.
How He will remain - think about that.
Begin to talk to yourself. How He will remain - that is our challenge.
He does not remain in us when He is grieved.
I told you about offence.
When we hold a grudge against our brother, we have already grieved the Holy Spirit.
Whatever offence in the past, whatever pain in the past, it is time now to let go.
You have to do that now - before you receive.
Viewers all over the world, wherever you are, whatever you are doing,
it is time now to let go of offence, pain of the past, unforgiveness.
Right now, let go!
I disconnect you, in the name of Jesus!
From that pain of the past, you are disconnected, in the name of Jesus!
Unforgiveness - you are disconnected, in the name of Jesus!
Right now, open your lips and begin to disconnect yourself.
You need a free spirit right now!
Begin to disconnect yourself, in the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, wherever you are, distance is not a barrier.
We say to that affliction, there is no hiding place; leave my people!
Leave my people!
You affliction, leave my people!
Are you on the sickbed?
Wherever you are - are you in a coma?
The Owner of your soul is commanding you to rise up!
You affliction, leave my people!
Leave their blood, kidneys, liver, bones!
I command you, in the name of Jesus!
Viewers all over the world, whatever satan might have used to connect you to himself -
your weakness -
your weakness could be your anger, pain of the past, unforgiveness;
whatever satan might have used to connect you to himself, right now, begin to disconnect yourself.
Disconnect yourself, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Satan, leave my people!
I command you, in the name of Jesus, leave my people!
You have no role; you have no right.
Leave my people!
I tell you, you have no role; you have no right!
Leave their health, finances, business, marriage, family!
Open your lips, command satan!
Viewers all over the world, this is your confession right now.
Wherever that affliction is still located, I command that affliction to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
You affliction, leave my people!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I command you, in the name of Jesus!
I can see you being healed!
My people, I can see you being delivered!
I can hear breakthrough!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Declare this from your heart: Thank You, Jesus, I know you have healed me.
I know you have delivered me. Thank, You, Jesus!
Continue to confess this with all your heart.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
You shall live by your confession!
Right now, begin to live by your confession!
Confess!
I know you have delivered me! Thank You, Jesus!
I know you have healed me! Thank You, Jesus!
Open your lips!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name